<issueslist revision="4"
            maintainer="Andrew Sutton &lt;asutton@uakron.edu&gt;"
            date="2016-15-06"
>


<!-- The intro block enumerates the introductions
     for each of the different documents generated
     by a the make_lists program. -->
<intros>

<intro list="Active">
  <p>Reference ISO/IEC TS 19217</p>

  <p>This document contains the C++ core language issues for the Concepts
  Technical specification which the Committee (INCITS PL22.16 + WG21) has not
  yet acted, that is, issues with status
  <a href="ts-active.html#Ready">Ready</a>,
  <a href="ts-active.html#TentativelyReady">Tentatively Ready</a>,
  <a href="ts-active.html#Review">Review</a>,
  <a href="ts-active.html#Drafting">Drafing</a>,
  <a href="ts-active.html#Open">Open</a>, and
  <a href="ts-active.html#New">New</a>.
  (See <a href="#Status">Issue Status</a> below).


  <p>This document is part of a group of related documents that together
  describe the issues that have been raised regarding the C++ Standard.
  The other documents in the group are:</p>
  <ul>
      <li><a href="ts-toc.html">Table of Contents</a> for all concepts issues.</li>
      <li><a href="ts-index.html">Index by Section</a> for all concepts issues.</li>
      <li><a href="ts-status.html">Index by Status</a> for all concepts issues.</li>
      <li><a href="ts-closed.html">Closed Issues List</a></li>
      <li><a href="ts-defect.html">Defect Reports List</a></li>
  </ul>

  <p>Section references in this document refelct the section numbering
  in document <a href="http://www.open-std.org/jtc1/sc22/wg21/docs/papers/2015/n4549.pdf">
  WG21 N4549</a>.</p>

  <p>The purpose of these documents is to record the disposition of issues
  that have come before the Core Language Working Group of the ANSI
  (INCITS PL22.16) and ISO (WG21) C++ Standard Committee.</p>

  <p>The issues in these lists are not necessarily formal ISO Defect
  Reports (DR's). While some issues will eventually be elevated to
  official Defect Report status, other issues will be disposed of in
  other ways.</p>

  <p>For the most current official version of this document see
  <a href="http://www.open-std.org/jtc1/sc22/wg21/">http://www.open-std.org/jtc1/sc22/wg21/</a>.
  Requests for further information about this document should include
  the document number above, reference ISO/IEC 19217, and be
  submitted to Information Technology Industry Council (ITI), 1250 Eye
  Street NW, Washington, DC 20005.</p>

  <p>Information regarding C++ standardization can be found at
  <a href="http://isocpp.org/std">http://isocpp.org/std</a>.

</intro>

<intro list="Complete">
  <p>Reference ISO/IEC TS 19217</p>
  <p>Also see:</p>
    <ul>
      <li><a href="ts-toc.html">Table of Contents</a> for all concepts issues.</li>
      <li><a href="ts-index.html">Index by Section</a> for all concepts issues.</li>
      <li><a href="ts-status.html">Index by Status</a> for all concepts issues.</li>
      <li><a href="ts-active.html">Concepts Active Issues List</a></li>
      <li><a href="ts-closed.html">Concepts Closed Issues List</a></li>
    </ul>
  <p>This document contains only concepts issues which have been closed
  by the Core Working Group (CWG) after being found to be acceptable
  extensions to the standard.  That is, issues which have a status of <a href="ts-active.html#DR">DR</a>,
  <a href="ts-active.html#TC1">TC1</a>, <a href="ts-active.html#WP">WP</a>, <a href="ts-active.html#C++11">C++11</a>,
  or <a href="ts-active.html#Resolved">Resolved</a>. See the
  <a href="ts-closed.html">Concepts Closed Issues List</a> for issues closed as non-defects.  See the
  <a href="ts-active.html">Concepts Active Issues List</a> for active issues and more information.  The
  introductory material in that document also applies to this
  document.</p>
</intro>

<intro list="Closed">
  <p>Reference ISO/IEC TS 19217</p>
  <p>Also see:</p>
    <ul>
      <li><a href="ts-toc.html">Table of Contents</a> for all concepts issues.</li>
      <li><a href="ts-index.html">Index by Section</a> for all concepts issues.</li>
      <li><a href="ts-status.html">Index by Status</a> for all concepts issues.</li>
      <li><a href="ts-active.html">Concepts Active Issues List</a></li>
      <li><a href="ts-complete.html">Concepts Complete Issues List</a></li>
    </ul>

  <p>This document contains only concepts issues which have been closed
  by the Core Working Group as duplicates or not defects. That is,
  issues which have a status of <a href="ts-active.html#Dup">Dup</a> or
  <a href="ts-active.html#NAD">NAD</a>. See the <a href="ts-active.html">Concepts Active Issues List</a> active issues and more
  information. See the <a href="ts-complete.html">Concepts Complete Issues List</a> for issues considered
  accepted extensions.  The introductory material in that document also applies to
  this document.</p>
</intro>

<intro list="TOC">
  <p>Reference ISO/IEC TS 19217</p>

  <p>This document is the Table of Contents for the <a href="ts-active.html">Concepts Active Issues List</a>,
  <a href="ts-complete.html">Concepts Complete Issues List</a>, and <a href="ts-closed.html">Concepts Closed Issues List</a>.</p>

  <p>Also see:</p>
    <ul>
      <li><a href="ts-index.html">Index by Section</a></li>
      <li><a href="ts-status.html">Index by Status</a></li>
    </ul>
</intro>

<intro list="Section">
  <p>Reference ISO/IEC TS 19217</p>

  <p>This document is the Index by Section for the <a href="ts-active.html">Concepts Active Issues List</a>,
  <a href="ts-complete.html">Concepts Complete Issues List</a>, and <a href="ts-closed.html">Concepts Closed Issues List</a>.</p>

  <p>Also see:</p>
    <ul>
      <li><a href="ts-toc.html">Table of Contents</a></li>
      <li><a href="ts-status.html">Index by Status</a></li>
    </ul>
</intro>

<intro list="Status">
  <p>Reference ISO/IEC TS 19217</p>

  <p>This document is the Index by Status for the <a href="ts-active.html">Concepts Active Issues List</a>,
  <a href="ts-complete.html">Concepts Complete Issues List</a>, and <a href="ts-closed.html">Concepts Closed Issues List</a>.</p>

  <p>Also see:</p>
    <ul>
      <li><a href="ts-toc.html">Table of Contents</a></li>
      <li><a href="ts-index.html">Index by Section</a></li>
    </ul>
</intro>

</intros>


<revision_history>
</revision_history>

<statuses>

  <p>Issues progress through various statuses as the Core Language Working Group
  and, ultimately, the full PL22.16 and WG21 committees deliberate and act. For
  ease of reference, issues are grouped in these documents by their status.
  Issues have one of the following statuses:</p>

  <p><b>Open</b>: The issue is new or the working group has not yet formed an
  opinion on the issue. If a Suggested Resolution is given, it reflects the
  opinion of the issue's submitter, not necessarily that of the working group
  or the Committee as a whole.</p>

  <p><b>Drafting</b>: Informal consensus has been reached in the working group
  and is described in rough terms in a Tentative Resolution, although precise
  wording for the change is not yet available.</p>

  <p><b>Review</b>: Exact wording of a Proposed Resolution is now available for
  an issue on which the working group previously reached informal consensus.</p>

  <p><b>Ready</b>: The working group has reached consensus that a change in the
  working draft is required, the Proposed Resolution is correct, and the issue
  is ready to forward to the full Committee for ratification.

  <p><b>Tentatively Ready</b>: Like "ready" except that the resolution was
  produced and approved by a subset of the working group membership between
  meetings. Persons not participating in these between-meeting activities are
  encouraged to review such resolutions carefully and to alert the working
  group with any problems that may be found.</p>

  <p><b>DR</b>: The full Committee has approved the item as a proposed defect
  report. The Proposed Resolution in an issue with this status reflects the
  best judgment of the Committee at this time regarding the action that will
  be taken to remedy the defect; however, the current wording of the Standard
  remains in effect until such time as a Technical Corrigendum or a revision
  of the Standard is issued by ISO.</p>

  <p><b>Accepted</b>: Like a DR except that the issue concerns the wording of 
  the current Working Paper rather than that of the current International 
  Standard.</p>

  <p><b>WP</b>: An Accepted issue whose resolution is reflected in the current 
  Working Paper.

  <p><b>Dup</b>: The issue is identical to or a subset of another issue,
  identified in a Rationale statement.

  <p><b>NAD</b>: The working group has reached consensus that the issue is
  not a defect in the Standard. A Rationale statement describes the working
  group's reasoning.

  <p><b>Extension</b>: The working group has reached consensus that the issue
  is not a defect in the Standard but is a request for an extension to the
  language. The working group expresses no opinion on the merits of an issue
  with this status; however, the issue will be maintained on the list for
  possible future consideration as an extension proposal.
</statuses>

</issueslist>
